**Full Stack Engineer** 

adonis.shrop@gmail.com (404) 427-6943 Henderson, NV Github LinkedIn Portfolio

# Summary

I am a Full Stack Engineer with proficiencies in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REACT and Node. I am also a 3-time Grammy Award-Winning Songwriter with over 20+yrs of experience in the music industry. The methodology and creativity that has allowed me to constantly create a completely new idea and maintain success in music, comes from the same place with which I create and design beautiful web apps that are supremely user-friendly.

### **Skills**

Front End: JavaScript, React, React Hooks, HTML5, CSS3,

Back End: Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL Additional Tools: Mocha, Chai, Github

# **Recent Projects**

#### Flashcard App | Flashcard

- Built a Flashcard app that helps studying and information retention.
- Tech: JavaScript, HTML, REACT

### Pomodoro Timer | Pomodoro Timer

- Designed a version of the classic Timer app.
- Tech: JavaScript, HTML, CSS.

## **Experience**

#### OWNER/CEO | Beat Street Inc./Bane Ent. (DISCOGRAPHY ON REQUEST) (Atlanta, GA)

Aug 2004 – Present

- Compose and write lyrics to songs for A-List Artists (J. LO, Beyonce, Mariah Carey, Usher, etc.) resulting in 12 #1 singles.
- Record and mix hit songs for The A Room Studios.
- Vocal Produce all artists signed to label and for outside production work.
- Won 3 Grammys for my work on Usher's 'Confessions' ("My Boo") and Mariah Carey's 'Emancipation Of MIMI' ("So Lonely/One & Only")

#### SALES MANAGER | *Elevation Solar* (Henderson, NV)

Jun 2019 - Aug 2020

- Recruited, Trained, and Managed a team of 19 Sales Agents.
- Scaled team from 75kw/month to over 300kw/month in less than 90 days.
- Self-generated over \$1 million in Residential Solar Sales in first 10 weeks at company.

## STAFF SONGWRITER/PRODUCER | Bad Boy Entertainment (DISCOGRAPHY ON REQUEST) (New York, NY)

Nov 2000 - Aug 2012

- Composed chart topping songs/lyrics for World Renowned Producer Sean "Puffy" Combs.
- Recorded sessions for A-list artists in Daddy's House Studios Manhattan, NY.
- Vocal Produced all artists signed to label and for outside production work.

### **Education**

#### CERTIFICATE, THINKFUL | Thinkful School

Dec 2020 - June 2021

- Learned Full Stack Engineering and complete web design toolkit that features JS, HTML, REACT, NODE.
- Ultimate mastery of each language and Library for use in Full Stack Web Dev.

#### SOUND RECORDING TECHNOLOGY, MUSIC | Alabama State University

May 1996 - June 1997

- Studied Sound engineering for recorded music.
- Recorded, mixed and mastered Smooth Jazz songs in State-of-The-Art Studio on campus.
- Learned the nuances of Compression, EQ, Reverb, Gate and how they affect vocal and instrument tracks.